字幕组
ZiMuZu.tv
我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来  我只是个普通的鉴证专员
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
but secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
在我打败极速并拯救了多元宇宙后
After defeating Zoom and saving the multiverse,
我跑回到了过去
I ran back in time
创造出了另一条时间线  闪点
and created the alternate timeline, Flashpoint.
我恢复了时间线原来的状态
I restored the timeline to how it was,
但发现有些事却不一样了
only to find things weren't as I left them.
我给我们的世界带来了新的威胁
I brought new threats to our world,
而我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
and I'm the only one fast enough to stop them.
我就是  闪电侠
I am The Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on the Flash...
我接触过暗物质
I got hit with the dark matter.
那肯定会对我有所影响的
It must have affected me somehow.
我们要回家了
We're going home.
我回到过去
I went back in time
创造出了另一条时间线
and created an alternate timeline.
沃利
Wally?
沃利  听到我说话吗
Wally? Can you hear me?
我叫爱德华·克拉里斯
My name is Edward Clariss.
竞争者应该知道对方的名字
Rivals should know each other's names.
我回来后  一切还是变了样
When I came back, things weren't the same.
我不信任你
I don't trust you,
而我不喜欢我不信任的事物
and I don't like things that I don't trust.
你永远都是巴里  而我永远都是爱瑞丝
You'll always be Barry, and I'll always be Iris.
而且我们总是能找到对方
And we always find each other.
-你又是谁  -我是炼金术师
- Who are you? - I am Alchemy.
炼金术师
-炼金术师  -你失败了  克拉里斯
- Alchemy! - You failed, Clariss.
还记不记得你小时候的那种感觉
Remember that feeling you got as a kid
对某件事情很期待
when you were so excited about something
以至于都无心想其他的事情
that you couldn't focus on anything else?
我现在就是那种状态  想着
That's me right now, thinking about...
我一直在想的事情
well, what I always think about.
艾伦
Allen!
别再颠腿了
Enough with the knee.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
我要去约会了
I'm going on a date.
你现在还不能走
Well, not yet, you're not.
知道吗  你不算是我的领导  朱利安
You know, you're not actually my boss, Julian.
但我是个老技术员了  我没记错的话
But I am the senior lab tech, and the last time I checked,
我们的工作时间是上午十点到晚上七点
the hours were 10:00 A.M. To 7:00 P.M.
不是到六点五十八  也不是六点五十九
Not 6:58. Not 6:59.
而是七...
But se...
还记得另一种感觉吗
Remember that other feeling you got
对某件事情很期待
when that thing you were excited about
但感觉时间过得非常非常慢
seemed to take forever to arrive?
想象一下  作为极速者
Imagine being a speedster.
一天就像一周
Days seem like weeks.
一小时就像一天
Hours seem like days.
而一秒钟就像...  你懂得
And seconds seem like... you get the point.
点
...ven.
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
鲜花
送货口
太过了吗  确实有点过了
It's too much? Yeah, it's too much.
是因为这个心  对吗
It's the heart, right?
太俗了是吧  稍等
It's too cheesy? Hold on.
爱瑞丝
好点了吧  还是
Is that better? That's...
更糟了
that's worse?
那还是心形吧
We'll go back to the heart.
不用  巴仔  等等  等等
No, Bare. Wait, wait, wait.
这个很漂亮
It is so beautiful,
你真好
and you are so sweet,
但今天晚上  我想跟你在一起
but tonight, I want to be with you.
是巴里·艾伦  而不是闪电侠
Barry Allen. Not the Flash.
所以
So...
所以不要提闪电侠
So no Flash talk.
不要用你的速度
No speed.
没问题
No problem.
好的  就从现在起
All right. Starting now,
闪电侠模式正式关闭
the Flash is officially off-limits.
那...
So, wow...
我们去哪呢
where are we going?
要给你个惊喜
It's a surprise.
闪电侠
第三季
第三集
你最近是要打算
Are you planning on donating a kidney
卖肾吗  还是说...
sometime in the near future or...?
卖肾
A kidney?
这个地方...
This place is...
别管价格
Don't look at the prices.
想吃什么就点什么
Just get whatever you want.
那么...
So...
嗯  这个...
Yeah, so...
工作怎么样
How was work?
超级忙
Yeah, super busy.
你呢
How about you?
朱利安让我写一份根据碳测定年代的报告
Well, Julian had me write up a carbon dating report.
然后是一份DNA测序报告
Then a DNA sequencing report.
还有几份化合物报告
A couple chemical compound reports.
他几乎把所有不想我做的工作
So he pretty much just gives me all the work
都交给我了  所以...
he doesn't want me to do, so--
我知道  谈这真是无聊
Yeah, I know, it's really boring.
不是  很抱歉  巴里
No, no. Oh, I'm so sorry, Barry.
我只是  我今天真的很累
I'm just-- it's been a really long day.
我知道  我也是
Yeah, I know. Me too.
出什么事了
What's going on?
看来对面街有人在抢劫
Apparently, a robbery's in progress across the street.
失陪
Excuse me.
快去  快去
Go, go, go.
-你确定吗  -没错
- Are you sure? - Yeah.
可以用你的速度  快去吧
Yeah, use your speed. Go.
好
Okay.
刚才说到哪了
Where were we?
是西斯科
Cisco.
我们该走了
We should go.
好
Yeah.
-怎么了  -那个
- What's going on? - That.
你怎么把缺口打开了
Yeah, why'd you open a breach?
-我没有  -什么
- I didn't. - What?
所以我们才叫你来
That's why we called you.
你能关上它吗
Well, can you close it?
再说一次  如果我可以  就不会叫你来了
Once again, wouldn't have called if I could.
-有人正要穿越过来  -往后退
- Somebody's coming through. - Get back.
艾伦
Allen.
威尔斯
Wells.
我需要你的帮忙
I need your help.
帮什么
With what?
帮她
With that.
大家好
Hey, guys.
杰西  你是极速者吗
Jesse. You're a speedster?
是的  帅呆了吧
Yeah. It's pretty cool, right?
是啊  我也这么觉得
I mean, yeah, I would say so.
是什么时候的事
When did this happen?
几天前
A few days ago.
在我帮艾伦夺回他的速度时
So, when I got Allen his speed back,
沃利和杰西被暗物质击中
Wally and Jesse were hit with the dark matter.
然后她受到了影响  完全受了影响
Turns out she was affected. She was totally affected.
但我却没获得速度
But I didn't get speed,
会不会是受到了别的影响
so could it have been from something else?
不  应该不会
No-- I mean, I doubt it.
暗物质在不同时间里
Dark matter affects different people
对每个人产生的影响都会不一样
in different ways at different times--
有时完全没影响  你就庆幸吧
sometimes not at all, so be thankful,
可她是受了影响  我要检查一下
but she was affected, and I want to run some tests
看看影响的程度
and find out just how much.
那你就来对地方了
Well, then, you've come to the right place.
我们去极速实验室吧
Let's go to the Speed Lab.
极速实验室
Speed Lab?
不得了啊
This is insane.
我有预感你从没来过这房间
Something tells me you've never been in this room before.
没
Nope.
等等  你从没...
Wait, you-- you nev--
艾伦
Allen.
就是说你又再次穿越回过去了
I suppose that means you traveled back in time again.
是的  可是...
Yeah, but--
我和你说了多少次别这样做
How many times did I tell you not to do that?
你倒是发现得挺快啊  哈里
You figured that out pretty quickly, Harry.
是的  韦斯特小姐  这很简单
Yes, Ms. West, it was easy
因为我们也从没来过这里
because we've never been here either.
-没错  -好吧
- Nope. - Right.
其他地球  其他的时间线
Other Earths, other timelines.
没错
Yes, exactly.
你什么时候回去的
So when did you do it?
在我们回到地球二之后吗
After we returned to Earth-2?
听着  哈里
Look, Harry,
只有几件事改变了
only a couple things are different.
那肯定  才不是
I'm sure. Not.
不是吧
Really?
你们地球二才开始流行说这种反话吗
You guys are doing not on Earth-2 now?
没  只有他一个人
No. That's all him.
好了  我们还是让杰西上跑道
Okay, let's just get Jesse on the track
看看她的能力吧
and see what she can do.
好  开始吧
Yeah, let's do it.
好了  瞧好了
All right. Check this out.
厉害啊
Damn.
她跑得飞快啊
She really can move.
是啊
Yeah, she can.
我要走了
I got to go.
沃利
Wally.
老天
Oh, man.
我去和他聊聊
I'll talk to him.
乔
Hey, Joe.
其实...
Look, it's just...
他没有速度会更好
it is better if he doesn't have speed.
这点你不必说服我
Oh, you don't have to convince me of that.
我最不希望的就是我的两个孩子
The last thing I want is two of my kids
在城市里呼啸来去  置身危险中
zipping around the city, running into danger.
因为他脸上一副很失望的样子
'Cause he looked pretty disappointed.
这和另一条时间线上发生的事有关吧
This is about that other timeline, isn't it?
不  我只是
No, I just...
我想你应该留心看着他
I think you should keep an eye out.
-晚餐呢  -快好了  约翰
- Where's dinner? - It's almost ready, John.
我每天努力工作就为了养活这个家庭
I work hard every day to provide for this family,
而我得到的就只有这个
and this is what greets me?
空无一物的餐桌
An empty table?
就不能多等五分钟
Just five more minutes.
我现在饿了
I'm hungry now!
而且对你说话的时候你再回话  孩子
And you speak when you're spoken to, girl.
明白了吗
You understand me?
我把你从孤儿院救出来
I saved you from the orphanage
而且我还每天供你吃喝
and I provide for you every day,
所以闭好你的嘴  弗朗奇  知道了吗
so keep your mouth shut, Frankie, you got it?
抱歉  约翰  弗朗奇不在了
Sorry, John. Frankie's gone.
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
我想找一些关于
I was trying to get some information
昨晚被路灯攻击男人的信息
about the man who was attacked by a lamppost last night.
过来一下
Just come here for a second.
那个  昨晚
So, last night.
我知道我们第一次约会不算太好
I know our first date didn't shatter any records.
我说  也不是很糟啊
I mean, it wasn't that bad.
其实有些...
It was...
好吧  确实也没好太多
Okay, yeah. It wasn't that great, either.
-就是有点  -无聊
- It was just kind of... - Boring?
无聊  确实
Boring, yeah.
我感觉这是我的错
Which feels like my fault.
也许我不用能力就有些无聊了
Maybe I'm boring without my powers.
不  巴里  你没有能力也很完美
No, Barry, you are perfect without your powers.
你真好  但是  你是什么感觉
That's nice, but I mean, what do you think it is, then?
你不会觉得是我们应该...
You don't think it's a sign that we shouldn't--
不是
No!
No.
太好了  因为我还想再试一次
Good, I mean, 'cause I do-I want to try this again,
越快越好
as soon as possible,
但是发生了这一切
but just with everything that's going on--
这新案子  还有威尔斯和杰西回来了
this new case, and Wells and Jesse showing up--
是的  不  巴里
Yeah. No, Barry.
我完全理解  我理解
I totally get it. I get it.
我大概也要关注一下
I should probably concentrate
追赶我的交稿期限了  所以
on making my deadlines anyway, so.
好
Cool.
-好吧  -好
- Okay. - All right.
好了  我得去...
All right, well, I'm gonna-
-好  去吧  -工作
- Okay. Yeah. - Work.
对  工作  好
Yeah. Work. Cool.
行  咱们等会见
Yeah. All right. I'll see you later.
不对  我要...
No, I was--
-对  没错  -好吧
- Yeah, of course. - Yeah.
好的
Yeah. All right.
这上面说事发当时你与你父亲...
So this says you were in the room when your father--
养父  约翰
Foster father. John.
对  养父
Right. Foster father.
你养父被落到公寓中的路灯击中时
You were in the room when he was struck by the street lamppost
你在屋内吗
that flew into the apartment?
是的
Yeah.
但是我不记得当时的情况
But I don't remember any of that.
他回到家冲着凯伦  我的养母喊叫
He came home and yelled at Karen, my foster mom,
让给他准备晚餐
to get him dinner.
你就是那时候断片的吗
Is that when you blacked out?
是的  我想是的
Yeah, I think so.
这以前发生过吗
Has that happened before?
你断片这种
You blacking out?
约翰能好起来吗
Is John gonna be okay?
他在中城医院
He's in Central City Hospital.
我...
I...
他伤得挺重
He's pretty banged up.
弗朗奇  我能离开一小下吗
Frankie, can you excuse me for a second?
-当然可以  -谢谢
- Yeah, of course. - Thank you.
-巴仔  -什么
- Bare. - Yeah?
-你找到什么了吗  -好  听着
- What'd you find out? - Okay, get this.
街灯的外层
So, the outer layer of the lamppost
只有半英寸厚
is a half an inch thick,
但即使要扳动四分之一英寸的钢铁
but to bend even a quarter-inch of steel
需要177吨的拉伸强度  所以...
requires 177 tons of tensile strength, so--
所以我们寻找的是有超级力量的能力者吗
So we're looking for a meta with superstrength?
我还不确定
Well, I'm not sure yet,
但我能找到的只有这些
but that's as much as I could find.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
-因为我出现了  -没错
- Because I showed up. - Yeah.
巴里的小推理只有一个漏洞
Yes, the only problem with Barry's little theory
那就是路灯上没有找到指纹
is there were no fingerprints found on the post.
再说一次  朱利安  不是我的推理
Again, Julian, not my theory,
而且超能力者是可以戴手套的
and the meta could've been wearing gloves.
或许是这样
Yes, perhaps.
但是路灯的弯曲程度表示
But the curvature on the post suggests
同样大小的力在
that equal amounts of pressure were applied
同一时间被施加在整个物体上
to the whole thing at the same time.
所以  除非你的大力士有六米高...
So, unless our strong man has a wingspan of over 20 feet--
是其他原因造成的
Something else caused it.
没错
Yes.
那是谁  长官
Who's that, sir?
那是弗朗奇·凯恩  受害者的养女
That's Frankie Kane, the victim's foster kid.
那可怜的孩子换过很多家庭
That poor girl's been in and out of homes for years.
听着  她说她不记得
Listen, she said that she blacked out
意外发生时的事了
during the incident.
-断片了  -是的
- Blacked out? - Yeah.
对很多收养的孩子来说  抑制自己的记忆
Repressing memories is a coping mechanism
是一种自我保护机制
for lots of foster kids.
是吗
Is it?
是的
It is.
可能是别的原因
It could be something else.
-你要干什么  -你要
- What are you... - What...
你好
Hello there.
Hi.
你还好吗
You okay?
嗯
Yeah.
要不要再给你倒杯水
Can I get you some more water?
好的  谢谢你了
Yes, thank you.
没事
Sure.
你们再给她找一个杯子吧  警探
Gonna need another glass, Detective.
跟着他
Follow him..
-看你能查出些什么  -你要干什么
- See what you can get. - What are you gonna do?
我要把这个弄完
I'm gonna finish this up and convince my son
然后告诉我儿子他不是当超级英雄的料
that he's not meant to be a superhero.
好主意
Good idea.
我怎么样
So, how'd I do?
血压  心率  代谢率都很好
Blood pressure, heart rate, metabolic rate all excellent.
你这速度还真快啊  姑娘
And you've got some serious speed, girl.
我觉得你没问题了
I think you're good to go.
别急着下结论
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
我还想再做几项检测
I still want to run a few more tests.
-比如什么  -比如再来点检测
- Like what? - Like more tests.
沃利在吗
Hey, so, is Wally here?
还没来
No, not yet.
好吧
Right.
那好  我要去弄点吃的
Okay, I'm gonna-- I'm gonna go grab some food.
我饿了
I'm starving.
工作室里有能量棒
Yeah, there's some PowerBars in the workshop.
-自己拿吧  -好
- Help yourself. - Cool.
-哈里  -怎么
- Harry? - Mm-hmm?
-你在干嘛  -我在详细检查
- What're you doing? - Being thorough.
是吗  看起来你这是在拖延
Yeah? 'Cause it seems like you're stalling.
好吧  我就是在拖延
Okay, fine. I'm stalling.
我在拖延  怎样
I'm stalling. So what?
不怎样  为什么这样做
So what? So why?
为什么这么做  为什么
So why? Why?
为什么  我还要给你们解释吗
Why? I got to explain myself to you two?
还真得解释  你们不是父母
Oh, I guess I do, 'cause you're not parents.
那是我女儿  好吗
That's my daughter, okay?
她待在这个地球上几个月了
And she spent months on this very Earth
她看着巴里·艾伦打败一个又一个超能力者
watching Barry Allen defeat meta after meta after meta--
然后又打败了极速  突然之间  砰
and Zoom-- and all of a sudden, bam!
她得到了速度
She's got speed,
现在她想当巴里那样的英雄
and now she wants to be a hero just like him.
我觉得这主意真是太棒了
And I think that's a great idea.
才怪
Not!
哈里  我们可以帮助她
Harry, we can help her.
我们可以像训练巴里一样训练她
We can train her just like we did with Barry.
我不想训练她  懂吗
I don't want you to train her, okay?
我带她来是想让你们说服她放弃这个想法
I brought her here for you to talk her out of it,
而不是践行这个想法  懂了吗  拉蒙
not talk her into it, all right, Ramon?
你去跟她谈谈  你是超能力者
You--you should talk to her. You're a meta.
正因为这个  我才最不适合说服她
Yeah, which makes me the last person
不去自己使用能力
she should talk to about not using her powers.
好吧  斯诺
Okay, Snow...
凯特琳
Caitlin...
你跟她
You and her,
你俩一直关系很好
you've always had such a special relationship.
你跟她谈谈
You talk to her.
-我们关系没那么好  -是吗
- No, we don't. - Yeah.
我对能力一无所知
And I don't know anything about having powers,
你最不应该找我说
so I'm the last person you should talk to,
别让我去
so don't ask me.
等等  我
Wait, I...
中城警局
老爸
Dad.
怎么了  你找我什么事
What's going on? Why'd you want to see me?
坐吧
Have a seat.
是这样
Look...
我知道看着杰西拥有速度
I know it's been really hard for you,
对你来说很难过
seeing Jesse with speed.
我一直在想哈里所说的
I just keep thinking of what Harry said.
有时候能力的显现需要时间
How sometimes it takes a while for powers to manifest.
是  哈里也说过有可能无法获得能力
Yeah, Harry also said that they may never manifest.
我也被暗物质击中了
Yes, but I got hit by that dark matter too,
和杰西一样
just like Jesse.
我也有可能获得能力
Could still happen for me somehow.
第一次粒子加速器
Look, you weren't here
爆炸的时候你不在这里
when the first particle accelerator exploded.
暗物质扩散到了整个城市
That dark matter went throughout the whole city.
所有人都受伤了
Everybody got hit.
我  你姐姐  这整个警察局
Me, your sister, this whole precinct.
你知道那之后出现了多少超能力者吗
Do you know how many metas there have been so far?
我知道你很渴望能力
I know you want this more than anything,
但你要接受现实  这可能不会成真
but you have to face the fact that it might not happen.
所以你觉得我该放手吗
So you think, just let it go?
不再去想帮助别人吗
Give up on wanting to help people?
没有超能力也能做到
You don't need powers to do that.
巴里早在成为闪电侠之前
Look, Barry was coming to the rescue
就以鉴证员的身份在帮忙了
as a CSI long before he was the Flash.
他那时就想帮助大家
He wanted to help people then
和你现在想帮忙一样
just like you want to help people now.
于是他投身学习
So he studied.
他聪明的脑袋越用越活
He honed that brilliant mind of his.
你和他一样聪明  小沃
And you have the same brilliant mind, Wall.
-爸  -说真的 儿子
- Dad-- - No, I mean it, son.
很多人都想
Look, a lot of people dream
让世界更美好
about making the world a better place.
你的头脑和工程才华
With that mind of yours and that engineering talent,
肯定能创造更好的世界
you literally could build a better world.
那又怎样
So what?
我该在学校学习
I got to stay in school?
对  待在学校学习
Yeah, you got to stay in school.
只需多待几年
Just a couple more years.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我想你之前提取过DNA样品
I assumed you'd taken a DNA sample before.
好吧 我知道你在做什么
Okay, yes. I know what you're doing.
我问为什么做这个
I mean, why are you doing it?
你又想偷样品了吗
Are you looking to steal another sample?
我分解出
I've isolated an element
五具外壳上都有的某种成分
consistent in all five of the husks that we've found,
包括爱德华·克拉里斯的
including Edward Clariss's.
你是说竞争者
You mean the Rival?
媒体是这样叫他的
That's what the papers are calling him, yes.
是什么成分
What's the element?
不知道
I don't know.
但跟我在其他超能力者
But it's not one that I've found
身上找到的样品不同
in any other meta-human samples that I've studied.
你认为楼下的弗朗奇
So you think that Frankie, the girl downstairs,
DNA里也有同样的成分
has the same element in her DNA?
如果没有可能
Well, I wouldn't be comparing samples
我也不会比对样品  对吧  艾伦
if it wasn't a possibility, would I, Allen?
还好我比对了
It's a good thing for both of us I did.
走
Come on.
怎么了
What?
-她在哪  -冷静  朱利安
- Where is she? - Calm down, okay? Julian?
姑娘  你站住
You! You, girl! Stop!
-冷静  朱利安  -站住
- Hey, ease up, Julian. - Stop!
-我  -你干的  对不对
- Me? - You did it, didn't you?
什么
What?
路灯柱是被你拔起来的吧
The lamppost. You did it, didn't you?
什么 不不 闭嘴
What? No, no, no, stop.
-你撒谎  -朱利安
- You're a liar! - Julian!
-你是超能力者  -闭嘴  不是
- You're a meta-human. - Stop, no, stop!
是你害你养父进医院的吧
You put your foster father in the hospital, didn't you?
-不不  -是不是你
- No, no! - Didn't you?
是不是你
Didn't you?
我不仅想伤害他
Oh, I wanted to do more than hurt him.
现在也要让你吃点苦头
Now I'm gonna do the same to you.
弗朗奇
Frankie!
弗朗奇  住手
Frankie, stop!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
弗朗奇
Frankie!
不  没有弗朗奇了
No. Frankie's gone.
我叫磁红女
My name is Magenta.
你这样全怪炼金术师
You're like this because of Alchemy.
他改变了你  对吧
He changed you, didn't he?
你不是这样的
This isn't you.
跟我走
Just come with me.
告诉我发生了什么
Tell me what happened.
我能帮你
I can help you.
我不要谁帮忙  闪电侠
I don't need any more help, Flash.
我只是不想让任何人受伤
I just don't want anyone to get hurt.
太晚了
It's too late for that.
弗朗奇  不
Frankie, don't!
放我走
It's me...
不然他就死
or him.
别
Come on.
中城综合医院 个人医疗记录
她叫弗朗奇·凯恩
Her name's Frankie Kane,
她自称为磁红女
but she's calling herself Magenta.
我见到的那个胆小善良的姑娘
That Magenta is a whole different person
跟这个磁红女可完全不同
than the scared, kind girl I was interviewing.
她有分离性障碍
She's dissociative.
你是说人格分裂
You mean split-personality.
她的医疗记录显示
According to her medical records,
她从出生就一直患有这个病
it's a condition she's been dealing with her entire life.
在中城警局被人吼叫肯定让她发病了
I'm sure all the yelling at CCPD is what triggered it.
《化身博士》中患有人格分裂的主角
杰柯尔是善良人格  海德是邪恶人格
所以弗朗奇是杰柯尔  磁红女是海德
So Frankie is Jekyll. Magenta is Hyde.
经典的善恶大战
Classic good versus evil.
电影主角因被认为患有人格分裂而免去罪行
或者她在演《一级恐惧》
Or she's pulling a "Primal Fear."
-她装的  -不  她没有装
- She's faking it. - No, she's not faking it.
我能感受到她内心的挣扎
I saw the struggle going on inside of her.
磁红女想完全控制她
Magenta's trying to take over completely.
你说她一直生活在寄养家庭中
You said she was raised in the foster care system.
对  从小到大一直居无定所
Yep, all her life. She went from home to home.
对  可能也不是很幸运
Yeah, and maybe not good ones.
她现在的养父叫约翰
Her current foster father, John--
在袭击中受伤的那位
the one who was hurt in the attack.
他有好几条行为不检的罪名
Yeah, he's got a few disorderly conducts.
中城家庭服务处 个人档案
他可能会有一些对我们有帮助的信息
He might have some information we can use.
我可以跟进他
I can follow up with him.
还有一件事
There is something else.
她从炼金术师那里获得了超能力
She got her powers from Alchemy.
我说出他的名字时  她知道这是谁
When I said his name, she knew who he was,
所以磁红女在另外的时间线肯定也存在过
so Magenta must have existed in the other timeline too.
炼金术师是谁
Who's Alchemy?
炼金术师医生是一个穿着斗篷的魔法师
Well, Doctor Alchemy is a magic man in a cloak
他可以恢复人们在闪点的超能力
who can somehow restore the powers that people had in Flashpoint.
那闪点又是什么
Okay, and what's Flashpoint?
我们把巴里回到过去救下他妈妈时
That's what we're calling the alternate timeline
创造的时间线称为闪点
that Barry created when he went back in time and saved his mom.
磁红女就是你时空旅行制造的又一个麻烦
So Magenta is another side-effect from your time trip.
你真行
Genius. Not.
不用再挖苦我了  谢谢
I don't need to be reminded. Thank you.
她有那些超能力
Look, anybody with those powers
还这么狂暴  一定要把她找出来
and as angry as her needs to be tracked down.
还得尽快
Fast.
好啊
Well, great.
快是我的强项  让我补充能量去
I mean, fast I can do. Let me just go carb-load.
他不是...你也别...
He didn't... That's... You don't...
斯诺
Snow.
帮帮忙
Please.
好吧  哈利  我会跟她谈谈
Okay, Harry, I'll talk to her,
可是我不知道该说些什么
but I don't know what I'm gonna say.
嘿  乔
Hey, Joe?
你有和沃利谈过吗
Did you talk to Wally?
他看上去还是有些失落
He still seems a little bummed.
也不可能睡一觉就好了
It's not gonna fix itself overnight,
但没事的  他明白的
but it's all good. He gets it.
-好吧  -我对你说实话吧
- Okay. - And I got to be honest,
那是老爸警察比较好的劝说了
it was one of my better dad cop speeches.
什么是老爸警察
What's dad cop?
有好警察坏警察  和老爸警察
There's good cop and bad cop and dad cop.
严厉但可靠  一针见血
Firm but reassuring. Cuts to the point.
我怎么不知道这个
I don't think I know that one.
因为我没用在你身上
Yeah, I didn't use it on you.
沃利和你不一样  巴里
Wally's different than you, Barry.
你就像是我第二个女儿
You're like a second daughter.
你从来都不会藏着掖着
You over-share your feelings.
但对他  我就要细致一些
Him, I got to be a little more nuanced.
好吧
Cool.
我逗你玩儿呢
I'm messing with you.
如果有弗兰基的线索了我会告诉你的
I'll talk at you if I get any leads on Frankie, all right?
好
All right.
第二个女儿  他说什么呢
Second daughter? What is he talking about?
抱歉
Hey, sorry.
你们说极速者总是肚子饿
You guys were not kidding
看来不是开玩笑的
when you said speedsters were hungry all the time.
杰西  在你冲出去找弗兰基之前
Listen, Jesse, before you speed off to find Frankie,
我只是想确认一下你是否真的准备好了
I just want to make sure that you feel like you're ready.
什么意思
Why?
有什么问题吗
Is something wrong?
测试结果显示什么了吗
I mean, did the test results say something?
没有  完全没有
No, not at all.
所有的测试结果都很好
All the test results have come back fine so far.
只是
It's just...
也许你该慢慢来
maybe you should take it slow.
明白了
Right.
就因为我是女的
This is because I'm a girl.
什么
What?
才不是呢  怎么会
No, not at all. Why?
巴里就不需要慢慢来
Well, I mean, Barry didn't have to take things slow.
他一有超能力
You know, he was stopping the criminals
就开始打击罪犯了不是吗
the second he got his powers.
为什么我不能这么做
Why can't I do the same thing?
我的意思是  你肯定觉得
Well, I mean, I'm sure you think
有超能力是件好事
that it's a great thing to have powers,
但是有时候也没这么好  相信我
but sometimes, it's not so great. Trust me.
我的意思是  如果我有了超能力
I'm just saying that if I had powers,
我也许会慢慢来
I would probably take it slow.
我爸让你来的  是不是
My dad put you up to this, didn't he?
肯定是他  这就是他的作风
Yeah. I mean, of course he did.
杰西
Jesse...
你不想我拥有极速  对吗
You don't want me to have this speed, do you?
所以我们才来这里  对吗
I mean, that's why we're here, right?
你不是想测试我  而是要让大家
Not so you could test me, but so you could get everyone
劝我放弃这个超能力
to talk me out of using my powers.
-我只希望你能... -平安
- I just want you to be... - To be safe, yeah.
你这句话说了一辈子了
Yeah, I know. I've heard it my entire life.
这次不一样
This is different.
这次太不一样了
This is way different.
是不一样
Yeah, no, it is.
我不是巴里  对吗
'Cause I'm not Barry, right?
对
Right.
你不是巴里
You're not Barry.
这次让我来和她谈
Let me talk to her this time.
她还在这里
She's still here.
我能感觉到弗朗奇想控制身体
I can feel Frankie trying to stay in control.
你说我能打败她的
You said I could beat her.
我说的是
What I said was
我可以把你曾经拥有的力量还给你
I'd return to you the power you had
让你把自己的痛苦给别人
to inflict your pain upon others.
但我需要弗朗奇放手我才能做到
But I need Frankie gone to do that.
你还记得你为什么找我帮忙吗
Do you remember why you came to me?
我来找你
I came to you
是因为你有能让他不再伤害我
because you showed me a way to stop him from hurting me.
让他看到磁红女控制着主动权
Show him Magenta is in control.
只要你做到这一点
And once you've done that,
弗朗奇也会知道的
Frankie will know it as well.
你在这儿
Here you are.
对了  你昨天去哪了
Hey, so, where-- where did you go yesterday?
我只是  不想打扰你的训练
Wha--I... I didn't want to interrupt your training.
好吧
Right.
反正以后也不会有训练了
Yeah, well, looks like there won't be much of that anymore,
因为我爸正要所有人
now that my dad is getting everyone
来劝我不要这么做
to talk me out of using my powers.
等等  你不是也为这个来的吧
Wait, that--that's not why you're here, right?
不是  不是
No, no.
是我自己想来
This is all me.
你没事吧
You all right?
其实这一切发生在我身上时
You know, when this whole thing happened to me,
你是
you were...
我第一个想告诉的人
you were actually the first person I wanted to call.
我在想会不会也在你身上发生了
Yeah, I was sort of hoping it happened to you too.
我倒是想呢  真的
I dreamt about it, believe me.
到底是怎么发生的
How did this all happen?
当时情况很紧急
I mean, it was crazy.
有一天
So, like, one day,
我正从朋友家往家走
I was walking home from a friend's house,
有辆车闯了红灯
and this car ran a red light,
向我加速冲了过来
and it was speeding right at me,
我就呆在了原地  基本就等着被撞
and I just stood there, frozen, basically waiting to be hit.
然后我环顾四周
And then I looked around,
发现我周围的一切好像都静止了
and everything around me was frozen too.
很安静  没有声音
It was peaceful and quiet,
但我感觉到  身体里有电流通过
but I felt this, like, electricity running in me.
所以我就跑开了
And so I ran out of the way.
我一直跑一直跑
I kept running and running, and I...
现在都习惯不停下了
I mean, now I don't ever want to stop.
所以你就是用刺激激活了超能力
So you basically just jump-started your powers.
我想算是吧  怎么了
I mean, I guess so, yeah. Why?
挺好的
It's good to know.
沃利
Wally!
你干什么
What are you doing?
激活我的速度  你拉我干什么
Getting my speed. Why would you do that?
我那是为了救你
To save your life!
也许本来就成了  杰西
It could've worked, Jesse!
不会的  好吗  听我说
No, okay? Look...
我认为不会的
I don't think so.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
说真的
Seriously,
你到底怎么想的
what the hell were you thinking?
你不能就这么往车前面冲
You can't just go stepping into the street like that.
你得用脑子
I mean, you got to use your head.
我又没事  巴里  淡定
Nothing happened, Barry. Chill out.
你不是都跟乔谈过了吗
Didn't you talk to Joe about this?
-所以呢  -所以显然你没听进去
- Yeah, so? - So it clearly didn't help.
要是杰西不在那里你要怎么做
What would you have done if Jesse wasn't there, huh?
不知道
I don't know, man.
因为你什么也做不了
Because there's nothing you could've done.
因为你没有超能力
Because you don't have powers.
家里就只能有一个极速者是吧  巴里
Only room in our family for one speedster, Barry?
拜托趁还没玩出人命你别再这样了
Please just stop trying before you get yourself killed.
-说够了吗  -你就不说点什么吗
- You done? - Do you have anything to say?
基本上被你说完了
No, you pretty much covered it.
-不能再这样了  -别再吼我了行吗
- This has got to stop. - Stop yelling at me, okay?
我救了他  你想要我怎么做
I saved his life. What did you want me to do?
这不是重点  重点不是
That's not the point. That is not the--
我知道重点是什么
No, I know the point!
你不想让我用我的超能力
You don't want me to use my powers.
-对  -好吧  但我也没必要待在这里
- Right. - Fine. Fine, but I don't need to stay here
听你继续吼我
and listen to this anymore.
别  杰西  杰西
No--Jess. Jesse!
别
Don't--
你跟她说什么了
What did you say to her?
我吗
Me?
对  就是你
Yeah. You.
你怎么能怪我呢
Don't blame me for this.
我是真想帮忙
I tried to help.
是帮她还是帮我
Help her or help me?
听着  哈里
Listen, Harry.
也许她不愿意听你的话
Maybe the reason she's shutting you out
是因为你就没想着去理解
is because you're not trying to understand
-她现在的经历  -我就不需要
- what she's going through. - I don't need to--
也许如果你能帮她控制超能力
Maybe if you helped her navigate her powers
而不是直接认定这会毁掉她
rather than just assuming they'll destroy her,
她就会找你帮忙而不是避而远之
she'd turn to you rather than push you away.
我都不愿意在这里跑了
Can't even bring myself to take a lap around this thing.
为什么
Why is that?
你自己说的  这里一切都不同了
I mean, you said it. Everything's different here.
因为我改变时间线创造出
There's a guy creating meta-humans--innocent people--
把无辜的人变成超能力者的家伙
'cause I changed the timeline.
这都怪我
It's on me.
我大概知道
Yeah, I think I know a thing or two
那是种什么感觉
about what that feels like.
你知道吗  我总是犯错
You know, I keep making mistakes.
我犯了错  然后我就想
I make mistakes, and then I want
弥补我的错误
to make up for my mistakes.
于是我就犯下了更多错误
Then I just make more mistakes.
接着连我的女儿
Next thing I know, I have a daughter
都不愿跟我说话了
that won't even speak to me.
当我们一心想帮忙
How do we keep from messing things up
要如何避免搞砸事情
when all we want to do is help?
我不知道
I don't know.
但你曾经确实告诉过我
But you did once tell me that
你得相信从长远看来
you have to trust it in the long run
你做的决定是对的
the decisions you make are the right ones.
是啊
Yeah.
我总是太擅长原谅自己  艾伦
I was always too good at forgiving myself, Allen.
而你一直不太擅长
You were never good enough.
正门
是约翰·詹姆斯吗
John James?
是谁在问我
Who's asking?
你好  我是爱瑞丝·韦斯特
Hi, I'm Iris West.
我是《中城新闻图报》的记者
I'm a reporter for Central City Picture News.
我想问你几个关于弗朗奇·凯恩的问题
I wanted to ask you a couple questions about Frankie Kane.
他们找到她了吗
They find her yet?
我想还没找到
I don't believe so, no.
怎么会花这么久的时间
Well, what the hell's taking so long?
那个该死的超能力怪胎差点杀了我
That damn meta-human freak nearly killed me.
我知道  很遗憾
I know. I'm sorry.
我收留弗朗奇就得到这样的回报吗
That's what I get for taking Frankie in, huh? This?
上帝保佑我让我再见到她
God help me if I ever see her again.
那是什么意思
What does that mean?
就是得换她躺在医院了
It means that she's gonna be the one in the hospital.
严厉的爱啊
Tough love, John?
是啊  你说得太对了
Yeah, you're damn right.
她是在报复你伤害了她
She was getting back at you for hurting her.
而且她会再度尝试
And she's gonna try it again.
护士
Nurse!
我们得把这个男人转移到安全地点
We need to get this man to a safe location.
为什么
Why?
那声音是怎么回事
What the hell's that?
我的上帝啊
Oh, my God.
你要带我去哪
Where are you taking me?
弗朗奇来找你了
Frankie is coming for you.
尽管我很不情愿帮
And as much as it pains me
你这样的虐待狂混蛋
to help an abusive dick like you,
但我不能让你死
I can't let you die.
那是什么警报
What kind of alarm is that?
那是爱瑞丝的紧急按钮
That's Iris's panic button.
-她的什么  -她的紧急按钮
- Her what? - Her panic button.
我们给每个人的手机都安上了
We installed them on everyone's phones.
因为我们一直有人被绑架
'Cause we kept getting kidnapped.
至少在这个时间线还是有些进步的
At least something's an improvement in this timeline.
是那间医院
That's the hospital.
弗朗奇的养父在那里
Frankie's foster father's there.
是的  爱瑞丝去见他了
Yeah, and Iris went to see him.
看起来她不是唯一去见他的人
Looks like she's not the only one.
目标数据
等级/油轮
货轮
-那是艘油轮吗  -那是油轮  没错
- Is that a tanker? - Th-th-that's a tanker, yeah.
她会把他和楼里的人都杀死的
She's gonna kill him and everyone else in there.
-我得过去  -你打算怎么办
- I got to go. - What are you gonna do?
你又没有超级力量
You don't have superstrength.
赶紧开始想
Start thinking.
伙计们
Guys...
我来不及把所有人从医院里
There's not enough time to get everybody
救出来
out of the hospital.
这东西要砸过来了
This thing's coming down.
巴里  爱瑞丝还在楼里
Barry, Iris is still in there.
如果我制造一个导风漏斗如何
What if-- what if I create a wind funnel?
你制造的上升气流不够拖住那艘油轮
You won't be creating enough updraft to keep that tanker up.
不不  不是用双臂  如果我跑的话
No, no. Not with my arms. If I run.
-那应该  -螺旋桨效应
- That could... - Propeller.
行得通  巴里
That could work. Barry!
跑八字形  制造螺旋桨效应
Run in a figure eight fashion. You'll act like a propeller.
风会自己产生
The wind will build upon itself.
这会带来我们所需的超音速阻力
It'll create the supersonic resistance we need.
行得通
Could work.
好吧
All right.
再见了  爸爸
Bye-bye, Daddy.
闪电侠
Flash!
好了  成功了  但现在怎么办
Okay, well, that worked, but now what?
他如果一直待在上面就无法阻止她
He can't stop her if he's up there.
西斯科说得没错
Cisco's right.
去帮他
Go help him.
爸爸
Dad.
你得现在赶紧过去
You need to get out there, now.
-你确定吗  -是的  我确定
- Are you sure? - Yes, I'm sure.
我知道你能行
I know you can do it.
你不仅拥有够快的速度
You're more than fast enough.
跑吧  杰西
Now, run, Jesse.
跑
Run!
要不要助你一臂之力
Hey, thought you could use a little help.
这里交给我  你去对付她
I got this. You go take care of her.
磁红女
Magenta!
我有人帮助了
I got a little help.
好让我能帮助你
So I could help you.
好了  杀死你的养父
Okay, killing your foster father
以及医院里的所有人
and everyone else inside that hospital
并不会满足你的需要
isn't gonna give you what you need.
你根本不知道我需要什么
You have no idea what I need!
我想除掉的不只有约翰
It's not just John that I want to get rid of.
我想让他俩都消失
I want them both gone.
巴里  你得快阻止她
Barry, you got to stop her now.
油轮快掉下来了
That tanker's coming down!
我知道你还在  弗朗奇
I know you're still in there, Frankie.
不要让约翰毁掉你仍有的良知
Don't let John destroy the good that's still inside you.
他说我软弱
He said I was weak.
说我可悲
That I was pathetic!
他说我是个烂人
He said I was a horrible person.
他只是把自己一生的不幸遭遇
He's just blaming you for all the bad things
怪罪到你身上了
he's caused in his life.
那不是你的错
It's not your fault.
这一切不是你造成的
This isn't because of you.
我只想让他不再伤害我
I just want him to stop hurting me.
这不是解决办法
This isn't the way.
你的养父永远不会原谅自己的过错
Your foster father never forgave himself for his mistakes.
因此他才发泄到你身上
That's why he took them out on you.
他没法直面自己
He couldn't face who he is.
他没法向前看
He couldn't move forward.
但你可以
But you can.
他们成功了
They did it.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
没事的
It's okay.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
会没事的
It's gonna be okay.
没事的  会好起来的
It's okay. It's gonna be okay.
没有别人受伤了吧
So no one else got hurt?
很幸运  没有
Luckily, no.
你不用担心了
You don't have to worry about that.
那约翰呢
What about John?
地检官会就他的行为起诉他
The DA's prosecuting him for what he did to you.
所以他应该会面临服刑
So I think he's gonna be serving time,
他再也当不上任何人的养父了
and he's not gonna ever be anybody's foster father again.
这真的...
It's just so
制造了这一切却完全不记得
strange being responsible for all of this
这感觉真的很奇怪
and not remembering any of it.
你记得什么
What do you remember
你是怎么获得超能力的
about how you got your powers?
这一切是怎么开始的
How this all began?
起初我晚上会做梦  梦到磁红女
I started having dreams, at night, of Magenta.
-梦  -不仅仅是梦
- Dreams? - They were more than dreams.
就像我活在另一个人的世界似的
It was like I was living another life or something.
之后这些梦就会一直出现
And then I started getting them all the time.
在白天也会
During the day.
梦一次又一次出现
And the more it happened,
一次比一次更让人痛苦
the more painful they became.
之后我会听到一个声音
Then I started hearing a voice.
什么声音
What voice?
是个男人
It was a man.
叫炼金术师
Named Alchemy.
他说可以满足我的需要
He said he could give me what I wanted
让我再次强大起来
and make me powerful again.
我不明白
I didn't understand.
我以为我疯了
I thought I was going crazy.
相信我  磁红女的出现
Trust me. Magenta is not here
并不是你自身的原因
because of anything that you did.
你的内心或许有一丝阴暗
There may be a darkness inside of you,
但倘若你肯面对
but if you face it,
就会让你内心善良的一面占据优势
it'll make it easier for the good side of you to win.
你要放我走
You're letting me go?
这都不是你的错  弗朗奇
None of this is your fault, Frankie.
凯特琳在楔石城给你找了个好人家
Caitlin found you a good home in Keystone.
那里的人不会伤害你
People there will never hurt you.
可如果磁红女想要回来呢
But what if Magenta tries to come back?
打败她
Fight her.
你需要帮助的话  我们会到的
And if you need help, we'll be there.
我们相信你  弗朗奇
We have faith in you, Frankie.
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢谢你们
Thank you all.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事
Yeah.
没事  我...
Yeah, I...
我只是很同情她  就这样
I just feel bad for her, you know?
-你确定  -是的
- You sure? - Yeah.
无需"老爸警察"
No dad cop required.
你听说了啊
You heard about that, huh?
是的  我听说了
Yeah, I heard about that.
大英雄来了
There she is.
你那时表现很出色
You were tremendous out there.
真的很出色
You really were.
我想这是你作为超级英雄的
I guess that's your first victory...
第一次胜利
as a superhero.
我的女儿
My daughter.
杰西·快客
Jesse Quick.
没错  但我能做到是因为
Yeah, well, I mean, I was only able to do it
你相信我  所以...
'cause you believed in me, so...
不  我早就该这么做了
No, I should've been that way a long,
老早就该  可是...
long time ago, but...
总有一天  你会明白
You know, one day, you'll understand.
你现在不必知道
I don't expect you to know,
但我永远会担心
but I'm always gonna worry.
我永远会小心翼翼
I'm always going to be cautious.
我永远会爱你
I'm always going to love you.
爸爸  我知道
Dad, I know.
我当然知道
I mean, of course I know.
我永远会爱你
And I will always love you.
就算你把我完全逼疯了
Even when you drive me absolutely insane.
那么
So...
我们回家去  还是...
Are we going home or--
我想我们再留几天
I think we'll stay for a few days,
做多几次测试
run a few more tests,
再看看这个适合你吗
and also to see if this fits you.
西斯科做的徽章
Cisco did the insignia.
斯诺觉得这能帮到你
Snow thought this would help you, and
我也这么想
I agree.
-真的吗  -真的
- You do? - I do.
我的...我的...
My... My f...
我的恐惧
My fear...
我的内疚
my guilt...
一直以来
has kept both of us back
都在妨碍我们
for far too long.
你知道你一直都是我的英雄
You know you've always been my hero.
但现在...
But now...
我该让其他人也拥有你这个英雄
it's time for me to let you be one for everyone else.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你刚赶到
Hey, you just made it.
我要确保弗朗奇没事
Yeah, I had to make sure Frankie was okay.
那你准备好再来一次了吗
So, are you ready to try this again?
其实我想过
Um...actually, I had a thought
为什么我们上次的约会那么无聊
about why our last date was so boring.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
是的
Yeah...
送给你
Here you go.
我知道你认为我不该用我的超能力
So, I know that you think that I shouldn't use my powers,
但不是因为没了它们我就一无是处
and it's not that I'm nothing without them,
而是因为它们现在已成了我的一部分
but they are a part of me now, you know?
它们是你的一部分
They're part of you.
这是我们的生活  我认为
This is our life, and I think,
上次的约会  我们忽略了这部分
last date, we were ignoring that part of us.
我们努力做我是闪电侠之前的
We were trying to be the people that we were
那个自己
before I was the Flash,
所以才会搞砸
and that's why it wasn't working.
好  那么你想说什么
Okay, so what are you saying?
我想说我们不要再否认真实的自己
I'm saying we have to stop denying who we really are.
好  你所说的话
Well, yeah, I mean, when you put it that way...
我很赞同
I agree.
我们不能假装这一切都没发生过
We can't pretend like none of this has happened.
我知道你会那么想
I thought you'd see it that way.
抱歉
Sorry.
是乔  他要我回警局
It's Joe. He needs me at the station.
没事  你去吧
It's fine. Go.
-真的吗  -是的
- Really? - Yeah.
这已经是个非常棒的约会
This has already been a really amazing date...
闪电侠
Flash.
-怎么了  -你来了
- Hey, what's going on? - There you are.
辛格要我给你们看这个
Listen, Singh wanted me to show you guys this.
这是几天前铁山监狱的监控画面
This happened a few days ago at Iron Heights.
他们不想公开这件事
They tried to keep it under wraps
因为他们不想让人觉得
'cause they didn't want anybody to think
他们的安保有问题  但你看看
there was a security issue, but check it out.
是克拉里斯
That's Clariss.
炼金术师
Alchemy!
活着的克拉里斯
It was Clariss.
不  不  住手
No! Aah! No! Stop!
倒地之前就死了
Dead before he hit the ground.
炼金术师
Alchemy.
你听过这个名字吗
You ever heard that name before?
炼金术师
Alchemy?
没有  我没听过
No, I haven't.
也许是个隐形的超能力者
Maybe there's an invisible meta.
也许是个鬼
Maybe it's a ghost.
你相信鬼魂之说吗  艾伦
Do you believe in ghosts, Allen?
没有
No?
你觉得这也是
Hey, do you think this thing
闪点时间线的一部分吗
is part of the Flashpoint timeline too?
我觉得这些日子许多事情都是的
I have a feeling a lot of things are these days.